<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?><rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom"><channel><title>J0HN'S THINGS</title><link>https://joaopedrovbs.github.io/</link><description>Recent content on J0HN'S THINGS</description><generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator><language>en-us</language><atom:link href="https://joaopedrovbs.github.io/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml"/><item><title>About Me</title><link>https://joaopedrovbs.github.io/about/</link><pubDate>Sat, 25 Feb 2023 21:04:25 -0300</pubDate><guid>https://joaopedrovbs.github.io/about/</guid><description>Welcome to my blog!
My name is João Pedro, and I am a 25-year-old engineer from Brazil. I specialize in Embedded Systems, Space, and Robotics, which are fields that have always fascinated me. I have a passion for using my expertise in these areas to problem solve and develop cutting-edge technology that can help solve real-world problems.
My love for science and technology began at a young age, and after being to more than 20 robotics championships I pursued my passion by studying engineering at UFABC.</description><content>&lt;p>Welcome to my blog!&lt;/p>
&lt;p>My name is João Pedro, and I am a 25-year-old engineer from Brazil. I specialize in Embedded Systems, Space, and Robotics, which are fields that have always fascinated me. I have a passion for using my expertise in these areas to problem solve and develop cutting-edge technology that can help solve real-world problems.&lt;/p>
&lt;p>My love for science and technology began at a young age, and after being to more than 20 robotics championships I pursued my passion by studying engineering at UFABC. Since then, I have gained extensive experience in developing and implementing complex systems for a variety of applications. From designing electronic products for education to building Brazil&amp;rsquo;s first PocketQube Satellite for space exploration, I have worked on several exciting projects that have allowed me to explore the boundaries of what is possible.&lt;/p>
&lt;p>In my spare time, I enjoy reading and watching videos about the latest advancements in my fields of interest and keeping up with the latest trends. Through my blog, I hope to share my experiences, insights, and knowledge with others who share my passion for science, technology and engineering.&lt;/p>
&lt;p>Thank you for visiting!&lt;/p></content></item></channel></rss>